bluebottle.com 2011-12-07

# Bluebottle Email: Privacy

"I have been very happy with your service and would recommend it to any of my friends." - **Alex,** _June 2006_

"One of the reasons I went with BB in the first place was because of it's excellent spam protection, the anti spam service have always been performing for me 100% even though a lot of the other services have not." - **Gordon V,** _June 2006_

"I have to say that your service is remarkable!" - **_Mario S_**

"I would like to congratulate you on the changes to Bluebottle, especially because it will now display much better on a PDA screen." - **Rod L,** _May 2006_

"Thank you so much for your free email service. It is the only email I allow my children to use. The use of "trusted' senders and the ZERO spam allows me to be comfortable with allowing them to use email." - **Jennifer G,** _June 2006_

##  Bluebottle - the Only Anti-Spam solution you will ever need

**1** | **PRIVACY POLICY**  
---|---  
| This Privacy Policy: 

  1. discloses the privacy practices for the websites located at [www.bluebottle.com ](http://www.bluebottle.com/) and [mail.bluebottle.com ](http://mail.bluebottle.com/) (together, the **Website** ), solely operated by Bluebottle Solutions Pty Ltd ( **we** , the **Company** , or **us** ); and 
  2. sets out matters relating to the collection, use, disclosure and storage by us of personal information relating to our customers (the **Customer** or **you** ). 

| In this Privacy Policy, .personal information. means any piece of information which can potentially be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate a single person. Examples of personal information include, without limitation, your name, residential or business address, telephone number, IP address and email address.   
| We respect and value the privacy of our Customers.   
**2** | **CHILDREN**  
| The Website is not designed for children. Children under the age of 13 may not use this Website.   
**3** | **BECOMING A CUSTOMER**  
3.1  | In order to use the Website for the first time, you will be required to provide us with a user name, password, and a current email address. Based on this information, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password.   
3.2  | If, after we contact you about the services on our Website, you wish to purchase a product or service from us, you must provide additional personal information to us by electronically submitting an order form. This additional information will include, without limitation: 

  1. your full name, email address, residential or business address and a contact telephone number; and
  2. financial information such as your credit card number and its expiration date, and your billing address as per your credit card statement.

3.3  | We will only collect your personal information by lawful and fair means, and not in an unreasonably intrusive way.   
3.4  | When you submit an order form, you will be deemed to have consented to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.   
**4** | **COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE INFORMATION ABOUT CUSTOMERS**  
4.1  | Subject always to paragraph 12 of this Privacy Policy, once you have become a Customer we will only use and disclose personal information about you: 

  1. for purposes relevant to contacting you about the services on our Website in which you have expressed interest; 
  2. for assisting you with specific queries; 
  3. to manage your account and for all relevant billing purposes; and 
  4. if you have consented to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information for any other purposes, those specific purposes. 

4.2  | Unless you have specifically requested otherwise, we will only communicate with you by email.   
4.3  | We will use non-personally identifying information (such as browser types, internet service providers, operating systems etc) to compile statistics and improve the services we provide to Customers.   
**5** | **FINANCIAL INFORMATION**  
5.1  | The financial information you provide to us will be used only for billing purposes. If we have trouble processing your order we will contact you immediately.   
5.2  | We use outside credit card and payment processing companies to bill you for goods and services. The agents we use, and their privacy policies, are listed below:   
**6** | **PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURITY**  
6.1  | We are committed to keeping secure the personal information you provide to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. The personal information you provide to us is encrypted using secure socket layer technology.   
6.2  | While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. It is important to note that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Nevertheless, we take all reasonable precautions to protect the personal information we hold from misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.   
**7** | **OTHER SITES**  
7.1  | The Website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites.   
7.2  | If you use a forum, bulletin board, or chat-room on the Website, you should be aware that any personal information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for, and disclaim all liability in respect of, the personal information you choose to submit on these forums.   
**8** | **OPT-OUT OPTIONS**  
8.1  | From time-to-time we may provide you (via email) with the opportunity to participate in and/or receive surveys, special offers, newsletters and promotional communications. We will always afford you the option to opt-out of receiving these types of emails.   
8.2  | Any time after you have consented to the disclosure of your personal information for a specific purpose, you are entitled to direct us to no longer disclose your personal information for that purpose.   
8.3  | From time-to-time we may have to email you strictly service-related announcements (say, for example, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance). We consider the use of your personal information in this instance to be directly related to the service or product you will have subscribed for. If you do not wish to receive emails of this nature you have the option of deactivating your account with us.   
**9** | **PROFILE**  
| As part of the services we provide, we store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third party sources to create a .profile. of your preferences. We tie your personal information and your purchasing history to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the Website for you. Unless you specifically authorise us to do so, we will not share your profile with other third parties.   
**10** | **ACCESS AND CORRECTION AND INQUIRIES**  
10.1  | You can request us to provide you with access to personal information we hold about you. An access charge may apply.   
10.2  | If you become aware that the information we hold about you is inaccurate, incomplete, or outdated, please inform us so that we can correct it. Please notify us of any change to the details that you have provided to us. See paragraph 13 for details on how to contact us.   
**11** | **BUSINESS TRANSITION**  
| If the Company goes through a business transition, such as a merger or acquisition by another company, or the sale of all or a material portion of its assets ( **Business transition**.), your personal information may be among the assets transferred by the Company to the other parties to the Business transition. If a Business transition is contemplated you will, prior the Business transition completing, be informed of this development via email or through a prominent notice on our Website. If you are not satisfied with the outcome of the Business transition you will have the option of deactivating your account with us.   
**12** | **LEGAL DISCLOSURE**  
12.1  | Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, we reserve the right to disclose, without your consent, any of your information (including personal information) stored on, or sent via the Website, when we reasonably believe that such disclosure is required in any one or more of the following circumstances: 

  1. under or in relation to any law; 
  2. to protect the legal rights of the Company; 
  3. to comply with an enforceable governmental request, law enforcement request, judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process; 
  4. to enforce our Terms and Conditions; 
  5. to detect, prevent or investigate any potential violations of our Terms and Conditions; 
  6. to detect, prevent or investigate a matter relating to security, fraud or other technical issues; and/or 
  7. the disclosure is necessary to prevent or lessen a serious and imminent threat to the life or health of the individual concerned or of another person. 

12.2  | In the event that we disclose your personal information without your consent in accordance with paragraph 12.1 we are not obligated to inform you of such disclosure.   
**13** | **CONTACTING US**  
| If you have any queries in relation to this Privacy Policy, if you would like more details of what sort of personal information we hold, or if you would like to request access to your personal information or have a complaint about a breach of privacy, then you should contact us as follows:   
| Web Administrator   
Email : [support@bluebottle.com ](mailto:support@bluebottle.com)  
Telephone (International) : 61 421 511 933  
**14** | **CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**  
****|  We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Changes are effective once they are posted on the Website. You should periodically visit this page to review the current terms of this Privacy Policy.
